Speed - 20 knots
Heading towards open sea
死ぬなよ　小僧
Don't die, brat!
そ
の
重
い
足
を
膝
前
へ
導
く
sono omoi ashi o hiza o mae ni michibiku
That feeling pulls your feet onward,
その重い足を膝を前へ導く
负
责
人
Maki
负责人
chikara nanda tte Go ahead to
Telling you to go ahead towards a new power.
力
は
何
だ
っ
て
Go
ahead
問
う
力は何だって Go ahead 問う
kimi no naka ni shoujiru shoudou wa Treasure
That impulse born within you is a treasure!
君
の
中
に
生
じ
る
衝
動
は
treasure
君の中に生じる衝動はtreasure
honmon ka nisemono ka tsureteike yo
Whether it's real or fake, just take it along!
日
听
小
伍
长
田
Cris
翻
译
兰
樱
Naga
校
对
小
伍
江
本
物
か
偽
物
か
つ
れ
て
行
け
よ
日听
小伍
长田Cris
翻译
兰樱
Naga
校对
小伍
小江
本物か偽物か つれて行けよ
kuusou no kanata notte boku no mata mo taemai yo
Straddling the limits of this fantasy, my legs probably won't last,
空
想
の
彼
方
ま
で
僕
の
中
怠
慢
よ
空想の彼方まで 僕の中の怠慢よ
soredemo ii yo yume demo
But that's just fine, even if it's only a dream.
时
间
轴
阿
水
压
制
Coolkid
さ
ら
っ
て
も
い
よ
夢
で
も
时间轴
阿水
压制
Coolkid
さらってもいいよ 夢でも
todokisou de todokanai Make some noise
It seems within reach, but somehow too far off, so make some noise!
届
き
そ
う
で
届
か
な
い
make
some
noise
届きそうで届かない make some noise
Are these empty days gonna start shining bright?
kuukyo na nichijou wa kagayakidasu noka
空
虚
な
日
常
は
輝
き
出
す
の
か
空虚な日常は輝き出すのか
hakidasu you ni shite mae ni mae ni kogeba
If we push on through like we're about to hurl,
吐
き
出
す
よ
う
に
し
て
前
に
漕
げ
ば
吐き出すようにして前に前に漕げば
bokura no mirai wa kasoku shiteyuku darou
I'm sure our future will start to pick up speed!
僕
ら
の
未
来
は
加
速
し
て
い
く
だ
ろ
う
僕らの未来は加速していくだろう
今
こ
の
時
が
止
ま
る
と
し
て
も
ima kono toki ga tomaru to shitemo kono kokyuu made
Even if this moment in time becomes frozen,
今この時が止まるとしても
こ
の
呼
吸
ま
で
止
め
ら
れ
は
し
な
い
さ
この呼吸まで止められはしないさ
tomerare wa shinai sa kudaranai gohoubi mada?
There's no stopping this breath, so where's my worthless reward?
く
だ
ら
な
い
くだらない
ご
褒
美
ま
だ
？
ご褒美まだ？
本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 www.kamigami.org 和微博 @诸神字幕组
诸神微信公众号正式上线啦，搜索「诸神字幕组」添加关注吧
You call that a punch?!
なんだその打拳は
按摩にもなりゃしねぇ
It doesn't even count as a massage.
手前の格闘術はポートマフィアでも中堅以下だ
Your martial arts skills are
below average for the Port Mafia.
Your ability to neutralize
gifts is a nuisance,
異能無効化は厄介だが　この状況なら異能を使うまでもねぇ
but I don't even need to
use mine at this point.
立てや
Get up.
The party's just getting started.
招宴は始まったばかりだぜ
流石ポートマフィアきっての体術使い
You're not the Port Mafia's
top martial artist for nothing.
Whoops.
I thought my blocking arm'd get torn off.
防御した腕がもげるかと思ったよ
He blocked my hit with
his arm at the last second?
寸前で腕をあげ防御したのか
攻撃を読まれているな
He's predicting my attacks.
We've known each other for a long time.
君とは長い付き合いだ
手筋も間合いも動きの癖も完全に把握している
I already know your
moves, pacing, and habits.
でなきゃ相棒は務まらない　だろ
I wouldn't have been a proper
partner otherwise, right?
速い
He's fast!
だったらこの攻撃も読まれてるんだろうな
Then I bet you saw this coming, too!
打拳ってのはな　こうやって打つんだよ
This is how you throw a punch!
You thought you could beat me just by predicting my moves?
動きが読める程度で俺に勝てると思ったか
Tell me before you die.
最後に教えろ　わざと捕まったのは何故だ
Why did you let yourself get caught?
ここで何を待っていた
What were you waiting for here?
Heh, the silent treatment?
だんまりか
Fine.
いいさ　拷問の娯しみが増えるだけだ
I'll just have more fun torturing you.
The main reason
一番は…
is Atsushi-kun.
敦君だ
Atsushi?
敦？
The weretiger you're all obsessed with.
君達がご執心の人虎さ
I wanted to know who put the seven
billion yen price tag on his head.
彼の為に七十億の賞金を懸けたお大尽が誰か知りたくてね
身を危険に晒してまで？
You wanted to know so bad
you put your life on the line?
泣かせる話じゃねぇか
I'd like to say that's heartwarming,
と云いたいところだが　結果がこの態じゃあな
but look where you ended up.
「麒麟も老いぬれば駑馬に劣る」ってか
I guess even geniuses can
end up less than average, eh,
「歴代最年少幹部」さんよ
youngest executive in the Mafia's history?
Well, you've been deserted by lady luck.
まぁ　運にも見放されたってわけだ
なんせ俺が西方の小競り合いを鎮圧して
After all, you got caught
the very day I got back
半年ぶりに帰ったその日に捕縛されんだからな
from suppressing uprisings in the West.
俺からしたら幸運だぜ
From my perspective, it was a stroke of luck.
What's so funny?
何がおかしい
Let me tell you something that's good to know.
いいことを教えよう
There will be a meeting between
the top five executives tomorrow.
明日　五大幹部会がある
Impossible.
莫迦な
That's a meeting of critical importance
that only occurs once every several years,
あれは数年に一度
組織の趨勢を決定する時だけ開かれる
to determine what direction
to take as an organization.
極めて強制力の強い意思決定会議だ
If there were going to be one,
I would've been notified.
あるならとっくに連絡が
The reason it's happening is
a certain  letter I sent the other day to
理由は私が先日組織上層部にある手紙を送ったからだ
the upper echelons of the organization.
So, I'm going to predict this now.
で　予告するんだけど
君は私を殺さない
You're not going to kill me.
Moreover, you'll tell me where to
find information on who's paying
それどころか
懸賞金の払い主に関する情報の在処を私に教えたうえでこの部屋を出ていく
the weretiger bounty
before leaving this room.
And when you leave, you'll walk
and talk like a little rich girl.
それも　内股歩きのお嬢様口調でね
What?
My predictions always come true.
私の予言は必ず中る
I think you know that.
知ってると思うけど
この状況で何が…
What can you even hope for right—
A letter?
手紙？
You mentioned a letter?
手紙だと？
The letter said this:
手紙の内容はこうだ
"Should Dazai fall,
太宰　死歿せしむる時　汝らのあらゆる秘匿　公にならん
all of your secrets will come to light."
まさか手前…
You bastard! You didn't...
So now you've caught a former
executive turned traitor.
元幹部で裏切り者の私を捕縛した
But the package included a
letter to the upper echelons
けど上層部に
太宰が死んだら組織の秘密が全部バラされるよっていう手紙までついてきた
that if I die, all of the
organization's secrets will be disclosed.
検事局に渡れば　ポートマフィアの幹部全員を百回は死刑にできる
If the public prosecutor's office
gets a hold of those secrets,
all the Port Mafia executives can
be executed a hundred times over.
幹部会を開くには十分すぎる脅しだ
That's more than enough of a
threat to trigger the meeting.
そんな脅しに日和るほどポートマフィアは温くねぇ
The Port Mafia aren't so feeble that a threat like that would make them hesitate.
You'll die!
手前は死ぬ　死刑だ
There will be an execution!
だろうね
Probably.
But that'll be the council's decision.
けどそれは幹部会の決定事項だ
If you execute me before that
decision without permission,
決定前に私を勝手に死刑にかけたら
独断行動で背信問題になる
your unsanctioned act will be
considered an act of betrayal.
罷免か　最悪処刑だ
You'll be discharged or, at worst, executed.
そして俺が諸々の柵を振り切って手前を殺したとしても
And even if I look past all of
those factors and kill you,
手前は死ねて喜ぶだけ
you'll just be happy because
you managed to die.
So yeah, go ahead if you want.
ってことでやりたきゃどうぞ
Come on, hurry.
ほら　早く
Come on.
ま・だ・か・な
Oh?
なんだ
You're not going to?
やめるの
"Chuuya driven out of the
organization because of me"
「私の所為で組織を追われる中也」ってのも素敵だったのに
had a nice ring to it, too.
Don't tell me...
まさか…
The main reason
一番は…敦君だ
is Atsushi-kun.
ってことは　二番目の目的は俺に今の最悪な選択をさせること
So your second reason was to force me
to make that impossible decision just now?
Besides, why did you
come here in the first place?
そもそも君　何しに来たの
嫌がらせだよ
To harass you.
In actuality, you were waiting to harass me.
むしろ手前が俺に嫌がらせをする為に待ってたってことか
It's a reunion long in the making.
久しぶりの再会なんだ　このくらいの仕込みは当然だよ
A surprise of this caliber is only fair.
死なす　絶対こいついつか死なす
I'll have you killed.
I'll have you killed someday, I swear.
ところで　鎖を壊して私を解放したのは君だよね
By the way,
you're the one who broke
my chains and freed me.
If I just run away now,
私がこのまま逃げたら　君が逃亡幇助の疑いをかけられるよ
you'd be suspected of aiding my escape.
You bastard!
手前っ
君が云うことを聞くなら　探偵社の誰かが助けに来た風に偽装してもいい
If you do as I say,
I could make it look like someone
from the Agency came to rescue me.
Why should I believe you?!
それを信じろってのか
I don't lie in these kinds of negotiations.
私はこういう取引で嘘はつかない
I think you know that.
知ってると思うけど
手前　望みはなんだや
Bastard!
What do you want?
I said it earlier.
先刻云ったよ
人虎がどうとかの話なら　芥川が仕切ってた
If it's about that weretiger,
Akutagawa's leading the operation.
奴は二階の通信保管所に記録を残してる筈だ
He should have records in the communications
storage room on the second floor.
I see.
あ　そう
まぁ　予想はついてたけどね
Well, I had my guesses about that.
Oh?!
Just finish what you came here
for and get outta here, you ass.
用を済ませてさっさと消えろ　ったく
そりゃどうも
Why, thank you.
But I have one correction:
でも一つ訂正
今の私は美女との心中が夢なので　君に蹴り殺されても毛ほども嬉しくない
my dream right now is to commit
double-suicide with a beautiful woman,
so being kicked to death by you wouldn't
make me happy in the slightest.
Sorry.
悪いけど
Uh-huh.
あ　そう
じゃ今度　自殺志望の美人探しといてやるよ
I'll try to find a beautiful woman
willing to kill herself next time.
Chuuya.
中也
君　実はいい人だったのかい
I had no idea you were a good person!
早く死ねって意味だよ　馬鹿野郎
It's my way of saying go to hell, idiot!
云っておくがな　太宰
Let me tell you this, Dazai.
これで終わると思うなよ
Don't think this is the end of it!
二度目はねぇぞ
I won't  give you a second chance!
違う違う　なんか忘れてな～い
No, wrong!
Don't you think you're forgetting something?
Don't-you-think-you're-forgetting-something?
なんか忘～れてな～いかな～
I won't  give you a second chance!
二度目はなくってよ
なくってよって
N-No second ch-chance.
笑うとこだろ
You're supposed to laugh!
Huh?
あれ
Did you... come to rescue me?
ひょっとして…僕を助けに来てくれたん…
殺す心算で刺したが
I struck to kill,
不完全ながらも虎の治癒力が資されているか
but it seems the tiger's healing power
is in effect, if in incomplete form.
ここは…
Where am I?
Am I at sea?
海
You're on a smuggling ship that
carries weapons and munitions,
密輸船だ　武器弾薬を運ぶ
今日は貴様の為に貸切だが
though it's been reserved
solely for you today.
引き渡しまでの数刻　人生最後の船旅を楽しめ
Enjoy your last voyage for the next
few hours before we hand you over.
There's no point, I can't beat him.
こいつと戦っても勝てるわけない
隙を見つけて逃げないと
I'll have to find an opening
and make a run for it.
弱者は死ね
The weak will die.
死んで他者に道を譲れ
Die, and make way for others.
なんだ　僕に対するこの激しい憎しみは
Why does he have so much hatred for me?
外の世界に触れて心が動いたか　鏡花
Did you find yourself moved
by being in the outside world,
Kyouka?
彼を逃がして
Let him go.
Do you know what it's
like to be at the nadir?
どん底を知っているか
There is only the mire,
a foul stench, and self-pity.
あるのは汚泥　腐臭　自己憐憫
At times, someone will look
in from an opening far above,
遥か上方の穴から時折人が覗き込むが　誰もお前に気付かない
but no one will notice you.
With every breath, your
wretchedness burns your lungs.
ひと呼吸ごとに惨めさが肺を灼く
That's what's waiting for
you out there, Kyouka.
外でお前を待つのはそれだ　鏡花
Demon Snow is slaughter made flesh.
「夜叉白雪」は殺戮の権化
Yet you think you can live a normal
life outside of the Port Mafia?
そんなお前がポートマフィアを出て普通に生きると？
Weretiger, teach her what it's like.
人虎　教えてやるがいい
To help no one,
誰にも貢献せず　誰にも頼られず
to be counted on by no one,
and to live in hiding,
trembling like a worm.
泥虫のように怯えて生きるのがどういうことか
Continue killing, Kyouka,
殺しを続けろ　鏡花
as the Port Mafia's assassin.
ポートマフィアの暗殺者として
If not, stop breathing.
でなければ呼吸をするな
Worthless human beings don't
have the right to breathe.
無価値な人間に呼吸する権利はない
You may be right,
そうかもしれない
but
でも…
the crêpes were delicious.
クレープ　おいしかった
Where are you, brat?!
どこだ　小僧
Brat!
小僧
Kunikida-san?
国木田さん
So the Agency's found us already?
もう気付いたか　探偵社
Run while you still can.
今の内に逃げて
This ship isn't going to
reach the meeting spot.
この船は取引場所には行かない
Where else is it going?
ならばどこへ行く
The nadir.
どん底
Hey!
君
Run!
逃げて
Weretiger!
人虎
You set explosives in the armory?
まさか武器庫の爆薬を
You're trying to die, aren't you?
自決する心算だな
Is that man worth saving
at the cost of your life?
己の命をかけてまで救う価値のある男か　彼奴は
Brat!
小僧
Over here, brat!
ここだ　小僧
I can't come any closer
with those explosions!
爆発の所為でこれ以上近付けん　跳べ
Jump!
I'm making it out alive.
助かる　これで僕は
I'm safe now.
What are you doing? Hurry up!
何をしてる　早くしろ　船が沈むぞ
The ship's going to sink!
You idiot!
この怒阿呆
How much more trouble are you
going to cause the Agency?
どれだけ社に迷惑をかける気だ
Everyone's working unpaid right now!
社員全員只働きだぞ
What about her?
彼女は
Let that girl go!
あの娘は諦めろ
Not all innocent people can be saved.
善良な者がいつでも助かるわけではない
I've failed many times, too!
俺も何度も失敗してきた
That's the kind of city we're in,
and the job we have!
そういう街で　そういう仕事だ
She can't be saved?
彼女は助からない
That's right.
そうだ
We're not heroes.
俺達は超人ではない
I've wished so many times that we were.
そうならいいと何度思ったか知れん
But we're not!
だが違うんだ
Brat!
小僧
She...
彼女は…
She said the crêpe she
had with me tasted great.
僕と食べたクレープ　「おいしかった」って
She was told worthless human
beings have no right to breathe,
無価値な人間は呼吸する権利がないと云われて　「そうかもしれない」って
and she thought maybe that was true.
I don't think so.
僕は違うと思う
Because Dazai-san... the Agency...
didn't give up on me!
だって太宰さんは　探偵社は僕を見捨てなかった
I'm going!
僕　行ってきます
Hey!
おい
Run!
走れ
Run, Atsushi!
走れ　敦
Kyouka, is this the path you've chosen?
鏡花　これがお前の選んだ道か
Out of appreciation for your hard work thus far,
これまでの労に酬い
I'll lay you to rest.
楽にしてやろう
Die.
死ね
Face me, Akutagawa!
勝負だ　芥川
Episode 10
Rashoumon
and the Tiger
It now seems curious to me,
今となっては奇異なることだが
but I felt things between us
would end up like this eventually.
貴様とはいずれこうなる気がしていた
You'll miss out on the bounty.
懸賞金を取りっぱぐれるぞ
Don't worry.
気にするな
I had no intentions of handing
you over to them alive.
最早貴様を生かして渡す気などない
I can't forgive you.
お前は許せない
The same goes for me.
僕とて同じこと
Rashoumon!
「羅生門」
It's the same devoured space
that stopped bullets before.
前にも銃弾を止めたあの空間断絶か
As long as it's there,
my attacks can't get through.
これがある限り攻撃が届かない
How futile.
無益
Is this the best you can do, weretiger?
その程度か　人虎
Slow torture is not one of my hobbies.
嬲る趣味はない
If you must, curse your own weakness.
呪うなら己が惰弱さを呪え
You are a weakling who deluded
himself into thinking he was strong
貴様は探偵社という武装組織に属した故に　自らも強いと錯覚しただけの弱者
for having joined an armed
organization like the Agency.
Your membership was merely
due to coincidence and luck.
その探偵社へも偶然と幸運で属しただけだ
You're quite the talker today.
今日は随分とよく喋るな
I don't recall ever
identifying myself as a mute.
無口だと申告した憶えはないが
It's just like you say.
お前の云う通りだ
I am weak.
僕は弱い　けど一つだけ長所がある
But I do have one advantage.
And what's that?
なんだ
お前を倒せる
I can defeat you!
You reversed your tiger paws
to free your arms?!
虎化を解いた腕を
I thought so.
矢っ張りだ　空間断絶の防御は発動時間が掛かる
It takes time to activate
the devoured space barrier.
I'll just use my speed
to push my attacks, then!
ならこのまま速度で押し込む
What?!
なに
I don't have the time to play
along with childish fistfight
餓鬼の殴り合いには付き合えぬ
Sorry, but I'll just observe
your efforts from up here!
悪いがここから　貴様の奮闘を鑑賞させてもらう
Having this distance between
us works to his advantage.
この距離は奴の間合い　なんとか近付かないと
I have to close the gap somehow.
Shit!
しまった
There's less than five minutes left
before the ship is completely submerged.
船が完全に歿するまで五分も
He leapt using a fragment
blown from the explosion?
爆発の破片に乗って跳躍を
Your ability's slow to activate.
能力発動が遅い
The enemy won't wait for you to get up.
敵は君が起きるのを待ったりしない
Now, get up.
さあ　立て
Retaliate with your ability.
異能力で反撃しろ
That's not enough to
survive in the Port Mafia!
その程度ではポートマフィアで生き残れないぞ
Or perhaps you want to return to
being a stray dog in the slums?
それとも　貧民街の野良犬に戻りたいか
Good.
よし
Again.
もう一度だ
I have to take her to
Kunikida-san before the ship sinks!
船の沈む前に　彼女を国木田さんの処へ連れて行かないと
Why?
何故だ
Why is it you?!
何故貴様なのだ
Your ability is only newly
learned, a crude addition.
貴様の異能は所詮身に付けて幾許もない付け焼き刃
It's full of flaws, and you're not using it right!
欠缺ばかりで見通しも甘い
And yet,
だのに
why is it you?!
何故貴様なのだ
There it is again.
まただ
His hatred for me.
僕への憎しみ
Where does such hatred come from?
この凄じい憎悪はいったい…
I wonder if you can.
できるかな　君に
My new subordinate is much better than you.
私の新しい部下は君なんかよりよっぽど優秀だよ
I won't let him say that.
云わせぬ
I won't let him say such things ever again!
あの人にあのような言葉　二度と言わせぬ
Rashoumon!
「羅生門」
Higanzakura!
「彼岸桜」
Even if I've defeated him..
こいつを倒したところで
Wait.
待て
Why?
どうして…
My attack was a direct hit.
完全に入った　動ける筈が…
He can't possibly move.
You're so powerful.
お前はそんなに強いのに　どうして彼女を利用したんだ
Why'd you have to use her?
I didn't use her.
利用したのではない
「夜叉白雪」は殺戮の異能力
Demon Snow is an ability to kill.
Only when killing someone does
Kyouka's existence have meaning.
他者を殺す時のみ　鏡花は意味を得る
If she does not kill, she is worthless.
人を殺さねば無価値
I merely gave her value.
僕は鏡花に価値を与えただけだ
To make her worthy to live.
生きる価値を
That's the thing.
それだ
You don't get to decide whether
someone is worthy of being alive!
誰かに生きる価値があるかどうかを
お前が決めるな
Why couldn't you tell
her something different?
どうして彼女にもっと違う言葉をかけてやれなかったんだ
People need to be told they're worthy
of being alive by someone else
人は誰かに「生きていいよ」と云われなくちゃ生きていけないんだ
or they can't go on.
Why can't you understand
そんな簡単なことが　どうしてわからないんだ
such a simple thing?!
He tore Rashoumon apart?
羅生門を裂いた？
The tiger's ultra-regeneration!
虎の超再生
I can't let him get close!
奴を近付けてはまずい
I'll take him out at this distance!
この距離で仕留める
Rashoumon!
「羅生門」
Sawarabi!
「早蕨」
Akutagawa!
あ・く・た・が・わー
Rashoumon!
「羅生門」
Goku Mon
「獄門顎」
Agito!
Just fall.
そのまま落ちろ
The tiger's tail…
虎の…尾？
Devoured Space!
「空間断絶」
My new subordinate is
much better than you.
私の新しい部下は君なんかよりよっぽど優秀だよ
You big idiot.
この大馬鹿野郎が
Well done.
よくやったぞ
So,
却ー説　七十億も支払って虎を買おうとしたのは
who in the world wanted to spend
seven billion to buy a tiger?
どこの誰かなーっと
They're...
こいつらは…
It's time.
時間だ
It seems the bounty approach has failed.
Leader
of
The Guild,
A
Gifted
Organization
Francis F.
Leader
of
The Guild,
A
Gifted
Organization
Francis F.
懸賞金作戦は失敗か
The island mafia are such a half-baked lot.
島国のマフィアめ　とんだはんちくだな
Ability:
The Great Gatsby
The Promised Land will be
The Guild's for certain.
「約定の地」は　我々「ギルド」が必ずいただく
boku ga boku de irareru
I was searching for the reason
僕が僕でいられる　理由を探していた
riyuu o sagashiteita
why I'm able to stay as I am.
あなたの胸の中で　生きている僕がいるのならば
anata no mune no naka de
If there's a version of me
ikiteiru boku ga iru no naraba
that exists in your heart,
kurayami mo nagai sakamichi mo
Then even if darkness looms on this rocky road,
暗闇も長い坂道も　越えて行けるような僕になれるはず
koeteikeru you na boku ni nareru hazu
I'll be able to find the way to the new me.
それぞれに今を歩いてる僕らが笑えるように
sorezore ni ima o aruiteru bokura ga waraeru you ni
So that we can keep smiling in our own moments,
ikiteiru imi o tashikameainagara susumeru you ni
So that we can explore the meaning of life together,
生きている意味を確かめ合いながら進めるように
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
名前を呼ぶよ　あなたの名前を
あなたがあなたでいれるように
anata ga anata de ireru you ni
So that you can stay how you are.
kanashimi ni kurete anata no namida ga koboreru toki
Whenever you're overcome by grief, and tears flow,
悲しみに暮れてあなたの涙がこぼれる時
寂しさに溢れて心がしぼんでく時
samishisa ni afureta kokoro ga shibondeku toki
Whenever your heart floods with loneliness and you waste away,
名前を呼ぶよ　あなたの名前を
namae o yobu yo anata no namae o
I'll call out a name, your name.
僕の名前を呼んでくれたみたいに
boku no namae o yondekureta mitai ni
Just as you once called out mine.
A challenging task even the police passed on
警察でも投げた難題が　我が社に仕事の依頼として来た
has come to our Agency.
Atsushi, give it a try.
敦　やってみるか
Okay, I'll do my best!
はい　頑張ります
What?
なに　敦と一緒に現場に向かったのは賢治だと？
Kenji's the one going to
the job site with Atsushi?
こんなに早く手掛かりが掴めるなんて　賢治君凄い
I can't believe we already have a lead!
Kenji-kun, you're amazing!
Episode 11
...............................................................
l
An Unsuitable Profession for Her
An Ecstatic Detective Agency
Next time on Bungou Stray Dogs, Episode 11:
次回　「文豪ストレイドッグス」第十一話
First, An Unsuitable Profession for Her.
Second, An Ecstatic Detective Agency.
「其の一　彼女には向かない職業」
「其のニ　有頂天探偵社」
まずい　最強最悪コンビだ
Shit...
It's the best and worst team ever.